<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English Blog on My Lives</title>
    <link>/blog/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English Blog on My Lives</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:56:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/blog/en/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Bioconductor workflow</title>
      <link>/blog/en/2017/09/bioconductorworkflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/en/2017/09/bioconductorworkflow/</guid>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I found a very usful &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bioconductor.org/help/workflows/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;. Take time to work on it.&lt;/p&gt;

        
        &lt;script&gt;location.href/*Tal, could u pls not modify my script? It is not cool. Thanks!*/=&#39;/blog/en/2017/09/bioconductorworkflow/&#39;;&lt;/script&gt;
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent expression for Paper Writing</title>
      <link>/blog/en/2017/09/research_expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/en/2017/09/research_expression/</guid>
      <description>
        &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In recently years, high-throughput experimental techniques such as microarray, RNA-Seq and mass spectrometry can &lt;strong&gt;detect cellular molecules at systems-level&lt;/strong&gt;. These kinds of analyses generate huge quantitaties of data, which need to be given a &lt;strong&gt;biological interpretation.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://bioconductor.org/packages/release/bioc/vignettes/clusterProfiler/inst/doc/clusterProfiler.html&#34;&gt;Cite.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for &lt;strong&gt;identifying predominant biological themes of a collection of genes&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.disgenet.org/web/DisGeNET/menu/home&#34;&gt;cite&lt;/a&gt;
Through genomic profiling of 259 men with prostate cancer, scientists have identified five groups of prostate cancer with distinct DNA signatures.
The discovery represents a major advance as researchers can now begin trying to tailor therapies to those subtypes. The approach has worked well in breast cancer and helped millions avoid the unnecessary cost, pain and time spent on treatments that are destined to fail.
[Obama touts ‘lifesaving’ potential of personalized medicine]
Such work is the backbone of President Obama&amp;rsquo;s $215 million precision medicine initiative announced in January, which aims to pioneer a new approach to how we treat disease by moving away from a &amp;ldquo;one-size-fits-all&amp;rdquo; approach to medicine to one that takes into account things like a person’s genetic makeup, or the genetic profile of a tumor.
[A new way to study cancer and its treatments]
The prostate cancer study, reported in EBioMedicine, used samples from 482 tumors from those men, who were part of studies in Cambridge, Britain, and Stockholm. The scientists identified 100 genes associated with prostate cancer, including 94 that had not been previously associated with the disease.
Most importantly, they found that a small subset of the 100 genes predicted poor prognosis better than any other method that had been used in a clinic setting.
[He had a 3.5-pound tumor and months to live. Here’s how he survived.]
&amp;ldquo;For the first time in prostate cancer this study demonstrates the importance of integrated genomic analyses incorporating both benign and tumour tissue data in identifying molecular alterations leading to the generation of robust gene sets that are predictive of clinical outcome in independent patient cohorts,&amp;rdquo; the researchers wrote. They said this information could be &amp;ldquo;used for early detection of aggressive cases in a clinical setting, and inform treatment decisions.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
One of the most challenging problems in biomedical research is to understand the underlying mechanisms of complex diseases. Great effort has been spent on finding the genes associated to diseases (Botstein and Risch, 2003; Kann, 2009). However, more and more evidences indicate that most human diseases cannot be attributed to a single gene but arise due to complex interactions among multiple genetic variants and environmental risk factors (Hirschhorn and Daly, 2005). Several databases have been developed storing associations between genes and diseases such as CTDTM (Davis,et al., 2014), OMIM® (Hamosh et al., 2005) and the NHGRI-EBI GWAS catalog (Welter et al., 2014). Each of these databases focuses on different aspects of the phenotype-genotype relationship, and due to the nature of the database curation process, they are not complete. Hence, integration of different databases with information extracted from the literature is needed to allow a comprehensive view of the state of the art knowledge within this research field. With this need in mind, we have created DisGeNET.
DisGeNET is a discovery platform integrating information on gene-disease associations (GDAs) from several public data sources and the literature (Piñero et al., 2016; Piñero et al., 2015). The current version (DisGeNET v4.0) contains 429,036 associations, between 17,381 genes and 15,093 diseases, disorders and clinical or abnormal human phenotypes, and 72,870 variant-disease associations (VDAs), between 46,589 SNPs and 6,356 diseases and phenotypes. Given the large number of GDAs compiled in DisGeNET, we have also developed a score in order to rank the associations based on the supporting evidence. Importantly, useful tools have also been created to explore and analyze the data contained in DisGeNET. DisGeNET can be queried through Search and Browse functionalities available from this web interface, or by a plugin created for Cytoscape to query and analyze a network representation of the data. Moreover, DisGeNET data can be queried by downloading the SQLite database to your local repository. Furthermore, an RDF (Resource Description Framework) representation of DisGeNET database is also available. It can be queried using our SPARQL endpoint and a Faceted Browser. Follow the link for more information.
DisGeNET database has been cited by several papers. Some of them can be reviewed here.
The DisGeNET database is made available under the Open Database License. Any rights in individual contents of the database are licensed under the Database Contents License.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;an enormous collection of data sets
drives cancer initiation and progression
epigenetic plasticity 可塑性
patient cohort
readily intelligible to 容易理解

Alternatively authors 另外的作者

also known as

extensively cross-referenced to other resources 广泛的交叉 引用

Inferred orthologous reactions 推断同源反应

are statistically significant 统计显著

in a speed unmatchable by the human’s capacity of data procession
2.Complex genetic traits复杂的遗传性状 quite intuitively

DNA重排（rearrangement），基因扩增（amplification），点突变（point mutation） 真阳性（true positive）

coordinated amplification in the DNA （ DNA 扩增） overexpression in the mRNA （基因的过度表达） weak yet consistent 弱但是一致
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;邮件致谢10种表达 
邮件的开头  
感谢读者是邮件开场白的好办法。感谢您的读者能让对方感到高兴，特别是之后你有事相求的情况下会很有帮助。 
Thank you for contacting us. 
如果有人写信来询问公司的服务，就可以使用这句句子开头。向他们对公司的兴趣表示感谢。 
Thank you for your prompt reply. 
当一个客户或是同事很快就回复了你的邮件，一定记得要感谢他们。如果回复并不及时，只要将“prompt”除去即可，你还可以说，“Thank you for getting back to me.” 
Thank you for providing the requested information. 
如果你询问某人一些信息，他们花了点时间才发送给你，那就用这句句子表示你仍然对他们的付出表示感激。 
Thank you for all your assistance. 
如果有人给了你特别的帮助，那一定要感谢他们！如果你想对他们表示特别的感激，就用这个句子，“I truly appreciate … your help in resolving the problem.” 
Thank you raising your concerns. 
就算某个客户或是经理写邮件给你对你的工作提出了一定的质疑，你还是要感谢他们。这样你能表现出你对他们的认真态度表示尊重及感激。同时，你也可以使用，“Thank you for your feedback.” 
在邮件的结尾  
在邮件开头表示感谢一般是表示对对方过去付出的感谢，而在邮件结尾处表示感谢是对将来的帮助表示感谢。事先表示感谢，能让对方在行动时更主动更乐意。 
Thank you for your kind cooperation. 
如果你需要读者帮助你做某事，那就先得表示感谢。 
Thank you for your attention to this matter.  
与以上的类似，本句包含了你对对方将来可能的帮助表示感谢。 
Thank you for your understanding.

如果你写到任何会对读者产生负面影响的内容那就使用这句句子吧。 
Thank you for your consideration. 
如果您是在寻求机会或是福利，例如你在求职的话，就用这封邮件结尾。 
Thank you again for everything you’ve done. 
这句句子可以用在结尾，和以上有所不同。如果你在邮件开头已经谢过了读者，你就可以使用这句话，但是因为他们的帮助，你可以着重再次感谢你们的付出。 
Top ten ways to say “Thank you” in an English email 
At the beginning of the email 
Thanking your reader is a wonderful way of opening an email. It sets the right tone and makes the reader feel appreciated, which is particularly vital if you require future help from them. 
Thank you for contacting us. 
If someone writes to enquire about your company’s services, begin your email with this sentence. Show your appreciation for their interest in working with your company. 
Thank you for your prompt reply. 
When a client or colleague replies to a previous email in a short amount of time, notice and acknowledge this. If the reply wasn’t quick, simply removing “prompt” will work, or, you can opt for, “Thank you for getting back to me.” 
Thank you for providing the requested information. 
If you have asked someone for information, and they took the time to send it to you, use this sentence to demonstrate that you value what they’ve done. 
Thank you for all your assistance. 
If someone has gone out of their way to help you, thank them! If you want to offer more specific recognition for what they have done, follow this sentence with, “I truly appreciate … your help in resolving the problem.” 
Thank you raising your concerns. 
Even if a client or manager writes to express some concerns they have regarding your work, you can still thank them. This shows that you value their input and will take their concerns seriously. Alternatively, you may wish to use, “Thank you for your feedback.” 

At the end of the email 
While thank yous at the beginning of an email are typically written to thank the reader for past actions, thank yous at the end of an email tend to imply you are thanking the reader for a future action. By showing your appreciation in advance, you are more likely to get a positive reaction. 
Thank you for your kind cooperation. 
If you need the reader to cooperate by assisting you with something, then thank them in advance for their cooperation. 
Thank you for your attention to this matter.  
Similar to above, this sentence implies that you would appreciate the readers’ further assistance. 
Thank you for your understanding. 
Use this sentence if you’ve shared something that may inconvenience or negatively impact the reader. 
Thank you for your consideration. 
If you are requesting a benefit or an opportunity, such as when you apply for a new job, end your email with this sentence. 
Thank you again for everything you’ve done. 
This sentence, which is used at the end, is a bit different from those above. Use this if you have already thanked the reader at the beginning of the email, but due to their great efforts, you wish to thank them again for their past actions. 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

        
        &lt;script&gt;location.href/*Tal, could u pls not modify my script? It is not cool. Thanks!*/=&#39;/blog/en/2017/09/research_expression/&#39;;&lt;/script&gt;
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Test</title>
      <link>/blog/en/2017/08/sem_en1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/en/2017/08/sem_en1/</guid>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Nothing for writing. Just mark and test, so so..&lt;/p&gt;

        
        &lt;script&gt;location.href/*Tal, could u pls not modify my script? It is not cool. Thanks!*/=&#39;/blog/en/2017/08/sem_en1/&#39;;&lt;/script&gt;
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
